Next on the news, the two parts of the Atraxia heart, the famous jewel, were stolen.
Currently it is broken into two, but by combining them their value true value is realized.
They were in separate custody but,
they were stolen at almost the same time.
Currently the police is looking for trails.
I wonder where it's lover is.
Your acquintance isn't here yet?
So it was you.
Reiri Bunny.
Call me Rei Bunny.
If you want this then...
Try looking for it.
Where are you hiding it?
I wonder if it's here.
It's not there.
Don't be so violent.
Maybe in here.
Not there.
Woman are weird creatures.
This is not the thing you are looking for.
Yeah.
How about here?
Could these be fake and you are hiding it inside?
No way...
Not there either, huh?
Woman have another hole that a man doesn't
You noticed, as expected.
Eros the 3rd.
It is my defeat, so please be gentle.
Here I go!
I got you!
Back flip!
What!
You can't stop my libido with this.
Oh no!
Women have another pit.